export const flashcards = [
  {
    title: "Opening",
    front: `I could stand up here...`,
    back: `[DRY, SERIOUS, PRETEND TO BE A MORON]

I could stand up here,
and talk for hours and hours about Alex and Alex's many great qualities
Long pause
But no one wants to hear that… Especially on their wedding day…`
  },
  {
    title: "Introduction",
    front: `Introduce myself, it's an honour...`,
    back: `Good evening. everyone. I'm Leon, the best friend of the groom… For now.

It's an honour to be here.`
  },
  {
    title: "Speech Rules",
    front: `- Aim of a speech
- Kind, entertaining, or truth
- Choose one
- Heavy heart, let's begin...`,
    back: `I've always understood the aim of a speech like this is to:

* Be kind
* Be entertaining, or,
* Tell the truth.

But you can only choose one of them.

I'm afraid, Alex, I've opted for the T-word… the truth.

So, with a heavy heart, let us begin…`
  },
  {
    title: "Competition Setup",
    front: `- Competing with you
- Job
- Alex's CV`,
    back: `The most annoying thing about being Alex's best friend is that he is always competing with you.

* When we were 18, I got him a job at a cocktail bar where I worked.
* Now, I thought: "Great! My best mate is working with me. This will be fun." But three months later…
* Pause
* He was my manager.

If you take a look at Alex's CV, you'll notice it's written in size 72 bold font and just says the word "Legend"`
  },
  {
    title: "Pandemic Work",
    front: `- Years advance, mental age joke
- Pandemic story
- Wolf of Wall Street`,
    back: `[QUICK, WITTY]
Moving forwards, the years advance. Unfortunately, Alex's mental age didn't…

During the Covid pandemic, Alex lived with me and my partner in London.

* Naturally at the time, all work was remote, and we had this nook of the flat dedicated to office space. Nothing could go wrong.
* So, there I was, trying to read papers, translate mathematical equations into code. And Alex was hard at work too:
* Pause
* Blaring out Talksport, sending memes, and shouting something about deals.

Honestly, Alex thought he was starring in The Wolf of Wall Street.`
  },
  {
    title: "Change Coming: Footsteps Story",
    front: `- Something changed
- 2AM Doof
- New footsteps
- Something weird afoot
- Alex tricked someone into liking him`,
    back: `But towards the tail end of the pandemic, when things started to open up, something changed.

The thing about living with Alex, is that he tends to walk quite flat footed:

At 2 AM, I was used to hearing the sound: 'DOOF. DOOF. DOOF.'
Alex, the hunter-gatherer, returns from another night out with a chicken wrap in hand.
But then… a new sound: 'tap tap tap.' It was delicate. It was graceful… It was quite stealthy, but it was… the unmistakable sound of a second set of footsteps.

That's when I knew—something weird was, literally, afoot…
Alex had tricked someone into liking him.`
  },
  {
    title: "Alexandra Qualities",
    front: `- Not just anyone -> opposite sex -> not just... -> bestowed with qualities
- Getting to know her...
- She has built Alex up`,
    back: `And not just anyone.
A member of the opposite sex.
And not just any member of the opposite sex…
Someone as bestowed with qualities as Alexandra.

* Over time, I have had the chance to get to know her properly.
* She is intelligent, kind, and endlessly patient.
* Pause
* I mean, she did agree to marry Alex after all!

We are all here because we loved Alex before he met Alexandra, but undeniably, she has built him up for the better as well. 

Nobel Prizes have been given out for less.`
  },
  {
    title: "Parents",
    front: "To the parents",
    back: `So Congratulations to Mr and Mrs Reeves for raising such a fantastic daughter

* And to Jeremy and Theresa….
* Long pause
* Well, you did your best with what you had to work with.`
  },
  {
    title: "Being Crap",
    front: `- If I have ripped into alex too much: Reminder of the remit
- Truth extends further
- I am crap: Alex suffers me
- Wasted x, y, z and yet Alex ready to go again
- Alex is a true force of nature, nothing gets him down, calm and collected`,
    back: `So, if I've ripped into Alex for being a bit crap, I would like to remind you all of my remit in this speech: Telling the truth.

And, this truth extends further.

I should highlight that I am also incredibly crap, and the crucial thing is, Alex has always suffered me.

To abbreviate decades, I've wasted his time, patience, money – and much else - yet to Alex's credit, he's always relaxed and is ready to go again.

Alex is a true force of nature. Nothing gets him down - unless arsenal loses - and he's always been so confident and collected with everyone we meet.`
  },
  {
    title: "Final Truth",
    front: `- Truth is:
- Really tight growing up
- Separate paths
- That's okay because...
- Call back to 2AM joint steps - they will lead them onwards to a fulfilling and joyful married life`,
    back: `[EMPHASIS ON TRUTH NOW]
The truth is, me and Alex were really tight growing up, and my feeling is that over time life has taken us down separate paths.

And that's okay for me, because it's clear how brilliantly Alex and Alexandra have been in creating a life filled with adventure and happiness. 

Those joint steps that I heard at 2AM all those years ago have led them here today. And I am sure they will lead them onwards to a fulfilling and joyful married life.`
  },
  {
    title: "Toast",
    front: `- Love you both & honoured to call you friends
- No position to offer advice
- Enjoy yourselves & have enormous amounts of fun together
- Toast`,
    back: `Alex, Alex… I love you both and I'm honoured to call you friends.

And whilst I'm in no position to offer you advice, I simply wish that you enjoy yourselves and have enormous amounts of fun together.

So everyone, please join me in raising a glass, to the happy couple!`
  }
]; 